export const chapter = "Chapter - 15: Application of Future Tense";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct structure for forming an affirmative sentence in the Simple Future or Future Indefinite Tense?",
          optionA: "Subject + will/shall + Verb I Form + Object.",
          optionB: "Subject + will/shall + not + Verb I Form + Object.",
          optionC: "Subject + will/shall + be + Verb in III Form + Object.",
          correctAnswer: "Subject + will/shall + Verb I Form + Object.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the rules for Simple Future Tense, which subjects are associated with 'shall'?",
          optionA: "Only 'I' and 'we'",
          optionB: "Only 'he,' 'she,' and 'it'",
          optionC: "'I,' 'we,' and 'you'",
          correctAnswer: "Only 'I' and 'we'",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How is the Future Continuous Tense formed in an interrogative sentence?",
          optionA: "Subject + will/shall + be + Verb in I Form -ing + Object.",
          optionB: "Will/shall + Subject + be + Verb in I Form -ing + Object?",
          optionC:
            "Subject + will/shall + not + be + Verb in I Form -ing + Object.",
          correctAnswer:
            "Will/shall + Subject + be + Verb in I Form -ing + Object?",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which tense is used to show an action in continuity in the time to come?",
          optionA: "Simple Future Tense",
          optionB: "Future Continuous Tense",
          optionC: "Future Perfect Continuous Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Future Continuous Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct structure for forming an affirmative sentence in the Future Perfect Tense?",
          optionA: "Subject + will/shall + have + Verb in III Form + Object.",
          optionB:
            "Subject + will/shall + not + have + Verb in III Form + Object.",
          optionC: "Will/shall + Subject + have + Verb in III Form + Object?",
          correctAnswer:
            "Subject + will/shall + have + Verb in III Form + Object.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Future Perfect Tense, what does the tense indicate about the action?",
          optionA: "The action is ongoing.",
          optionB: "The action will be completed in the future.",
          optionC: "The action will be ongoing for a specific duration.",
          correctAnswer: "The action will be completed in the future.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct structure for forming an interrogative sentence in the Future Perfect Continuous Tense?",
          optionA:
            "Will/shall + Subject + have + been + Verb in I Form -ing + Object + Time Phrase?",
          optionB:
            "Subject + will/shall + not + have + been + Verb in I Form -ing + Object + Time Phrase.",
          optionC:
            "Subject + will/shall + have + been + Verb in I Form -ing + Object + Time Phrase?",
          correctAnswer:
            "Will/shall + Subject + have + been + Verb in I Form -ing + Object + Time Phrase?",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does the Future Perfect Continuous Tense indicate about the action?",
          optionA: "The action will be completed in the future.",
          optionB: "The action will be ongoing for a specific duration.",
          optionC: "The action will be continuous without any completion.",
          correctAnswer: "The action will be ongoing for a specific duration.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the Future Perfect Continuous Tense, how are time phrases used?",
          optionA: "Time phrases are not used in this tense.",
          optionB: "Time phrases indicate the starting point of the action.",
          optionC: "Time phrases indicate the completion of the action.",
          correctAnswer:
            "Time phrases indicate the starting point of the action.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which subjects are associated with 'shall be' in Future Continuous Tense?",
          optionA: "Only 'I' and 'we'",
          optionB: "Only 'he,' 'she,' and 'it'",
          optionC: "'I,' 'we,' and 'you'",
          correctAnswer: "Only 'I' and 'we'",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "In Simple Future or Future Indefinite Tense, the affirmative sentence structure is Subject + will/shall + Verb I Form + Object. For example, 'We ________ a taxi.'",
          options: ["shall hire", "will hire", "should hire"],
          correctAnswer: "will hire",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Future Continuous Tense, the negative sentence structure is Subject + will/shall + not + be + Verb in I Form -ing + Object. For example, 'They ________ beginning their journey tomorrow.'",
          options: ["will be", "shall be", "would be"],
          correctAnswer: "will be",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Future Perfect Tense, the interrogative sentence structure is ________ + Subject + will/shall + have + Verb in III Form + Object? For example, '________ we finished the work by now?'",
          options: ["Will", "Shall", "Should"],
          correctAnswer: "Will",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Future Perfect Continuous Tense is used to show an action in continuity in the time to come. The time phrases used are ________ and ________.",
          options: ["since, until", "for, since", "after, before"],
          correctAnswer: "for, since",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The correct structure for a negative sentence in Future Perfect Continuous Tense is Subject + will/shall + not + have + been + Verb in I Form -ing + Object + Time Phrase. For example, 'She ________ wrapping the gift for half an hour.'",
          options: ["will have", "shall have", "should have"],
          correctAnswer: "will have",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Simple Future Tense, the word order for an interrogative sentence is ________ + Subject + will/shall + Verb I Form + Object? For example, '________ you go there?'",
          options: ["Shall", "Will", "Should"],
          correctAnswer: "Will",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Future Perfect Continuous Tense is used to show an action in continuity in the time to come. The time phrases are used just like ________ Perfect Continuous Tense.",
          options: ["Present", "Past", "Future"],
          correctAnswer: "Past",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Future Perfect Tense, the affirmative sentence structure is Subject + will/shall + have + Verb in III Form + Object. For example, 'We ________ finished the work by now.'",
          options: ["will have", "shall have", "should have"],
          correctAnswer: "will have",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Future Continuous Tense, the rule is to use 'shall be' with ________ and 'will be' with all other Subjects.",
          options: ["I", "You", "He"],
          correctAnswer: "I",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which tense would you use the sentence 'She will have been wrapping the gift for half an hour.'?",
          options: [
            "Future Continuous Tense",
            "Future Perfect Tense",
            "Future Perfect Continuous Tense",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Future Perfect Continuous Tense",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Simple Past or Past Indefinite Tense is used to show a habitual action.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Continuous Tense is used to indicate an action that completed in the past.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Perfect Tense is used to show an action in continuity from a given time in the past.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Perfect Continuous Tense is used to show an action that began and completed in the past in comparison to another action.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Past Continuous Tense, 'Was' is used with all subjects.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Past Perfect Continuous Tense, 'Have' is used with all Singular Subjects.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Perfect Tense is used to show a habitual action in the past.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Continuous Tense can only express temporary situations.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Perfect Continuous Tense indicates an action in continuity from a given time.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Present Perfect Tense, 'Has' is used with all Singular Subjects.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
